In this video,
在这个视频中。
let's get started with the LocalDate. LocalDate today = LocalDate.
让我们从LocalDate开始。LocalDate today = LocalDate.
now( ). Make sure that you have the import in place because if you don't have the import, so you need to
now( )。请确保你已经导入了，因为如果你没有导入，那么你就需要
have the java.time.* in your imports.
因为如果你没有导入，那么你需要在你的导入中添加java.time.*。
So, if you restart JShell, you need to again import it in. So, import java.time.*.
所以，如果你重新启动JShell，你需要再次导入它。所以，导入java.time.*。
That's when you would be able to do LocalDate
这时你就可以做LocalDate了
today = LocalDate.now( )
and you can see that it's printing the
你可以看到，它正在打印
today's date. So, 2018-02-01.
今天的日期。所以，2018-02-01。
One of the important things about the LocalDate, is offers a lot of ways of getting information about
关于LocalDate的一个重要的事情是，它提供了很多方法来获取关于这个日期的信息。
this date.
这个日期的信息。
So, once we have created today, now I can get a lot of information about today.
所以，一旦我们创建了今天，现在我可以得到很多关于今天的信息。
Let's look at those methods now. So, let's say I would want to get the year.
现在让我们看看这些方法。所以，假设我想获得年份。
I can say getYear( ) and print 2018.
我可以说getYear( )并打印2018年。
I want to getDayOfWeek( ). It's printing Thursday.
我想获得DayOfWeek( )。它正在打印星期四。
So it says,
所以它说。
it says, today is a Thursday
它说，今天是星期四
and if I want DayOfMonth( ), so that prints 1, because today is the first day of February.
如果我想得到DayOfMonth( )，那么就打印出1，因为今天是2月的第一天。
So, today's date is 1st February
所以，今天的日期是2月1日
and if I want to print DayOfYear( ), it prints 32 because today is the 32nd day of the year.
如果我想打印DayOfYear( )，它会打印32，因为今天是一年中的第32天。
So, you can see that there are a number of methods which help you get information about the specific
所以，你可以看到，有许多方法可以帮助你获得关于特定的
date.
日期的信息。
So, I am able to get
所以，我能够得到
which day of the year, which day of the month,
今年的哪一天，每月的哪一天。
which day of the week, and all that kind of information just by creating a simple variable using the
哪一天，以及所有这些信息，只是通过使用
now( ) static method.
now( ) 静态方法创建一个简单的变量，就可以获得哪一年的哪一天，哪一个月的哪一天，以及所有这些信息。
You can also get details about the month.
你还可以获得关于月份的详细信息。
It's February
现在是二月
and if you want the number, you can get, getMonthValue which would return 2.
如果你想要数字，你可以得到，getMonthValue，它将返回2。
So, those are all the important methods in the API which would help you get information about the specific
所以，这些是API中所有重要的方法，它们将帮助你获得关于特定的
date.
日期的信息。
Now you might sometimes want to get some more generic information, right whether the year is a leap year,
现在，你有时可能想得到一些更通用的信息，比如，这一年是否是闰年。
how many days are there in that specific year, how many days are there in that specific month.
该年有多少天，该月有多少天。
The cool thing is, Java 8 DateTime API provides you all that stuff very easily.
最酷的是，Java 8的DateTime API很容易为你提供所有这些东西。
So, if I want to find out isLeapYear( ). All that I need to do is today.isLeapYear( ). Nope, it's false.
所以，如果我想找出isLeapYear( )。我所需要做的就是 today.isLeapYear( )。不，它是假的。
So, I am right now in 2018 which is not really a leap year, right. So, it returns false. I can find more information
所以，我现在是在2018年，这不是一个真正的闰年，对吧。所以，它返回错误。我可以找到更多的信息
about it. So, you can say today.lengthOfYear( ).
关于它的更多信息。所以，你可以说 today.lengthOfYear( )。
So, how many days are there in the current year? 365.
那么，当前的一年有多少天？365.
I can say lengthOfMonth( ), 28.
我可以说lengthOfMonth( )，28。
So, these methods help you get meta information about the year or the month we are in:
所以，这些方法可以帮助你获得关于我们所处年份或月份的元信息。
how many days are there in the month,
这个月有多少天。
how many days are there in the year, whether it's a leap year and things like that. And also, the date API provides
这一年有多少天，是否是闰年以及类似的事情。此外，日期API还提供了
ways to add number of days or number of months or number of years to your date. So,
提供了在日期中添加天数、月数或年数的方法。所以。
I would want to find out what is the date after 100 days. So, I can say today.plusDays(100).
我想知道100天后的日期是什么。所以，我可以说 today.plusDays(100)。
What's the date after 100 days?
100天后的日期是什么？
It says 2018-05-12,
它说2018-05-12。
right.
对。
So, it says 12th May 2018 is plus 100 days from now.
所以，它说2018年5月12日是从现在开始加100天。
You can also do plusMonths( ). So, plusMonths(100). So, 100 months from now is 1st of June, June
你也可以做 plusMonths( )。所以，plusMonths(100)。所以，从现在起100个月是6月1日，6月
2026 or you can even do plusYears( ),
2026年，或者你甚至可以做plusYears( )。
100 years from now.
从现在起100年。
Okay.
好的。
I will not be alive then, so 2118.
那时我就不在世了，所以是2118年。
These are all the methods you can use to add days, or months, or years to your date and you can also have
这些都是你可以用来给你的日期增加天数、月数或年数的方法，你也可以有
subtraction, right.
减法，对吧。
So, today.minusYears(100) or minusMonths( ) and  minusDays( ).
所以， today.minusYears(100) 或 minusMonths( ) 和 minusDays( )。
So, these are all the things to change the date. So, you can add the number of days, add number of months,
所以，这些都是改变日期的东西。所以，你可以增加天数，增加月数。
or a specific number of years to the date.
或特定年数的日期。
One of the important things that you'd need to remember is all these do not change today value. LocalDate
你需要记住的一个重要事项是所有这些都不会改变今天的值。本地日期
Time
时间
class is immutable.
类是不可改变的。
So, what we are doing in here is, we are creating new variables. The
所以，我们在这里所做的是，我们正在创建新的变量。而
today itself does not get affected.
今天本身并没有受到影响。
So, today minusYears(100) would be a new variable.
所以，今天减去Years(100)将是一个新变量。
So, I can say LocalDateTime, actually it's LocalDate.  LocalDate hundredYearsBefore
所以，我可以说是LocalDateTime，实际上是LocalDate。 LocalDate hundredYearsBefore
= today.minusYears(100).
= today.minusYears(100)。
The value of today on the other hand would still remain today.
另一方面，今天的值仍然会保持在今天。
It creates a new variable called hundredYearsBefore with the value.
它用这个值创建了一个新的变量，叫做 hundredYearsBefore。
So, this is immutable class again. All the methods would create new instances with the new value. Until
所以，这又是一个不可变的类。所有的方法都会用新的值创建新的实例。直到
now,
现在。
in this video, we have looked at a wide variety of things, right.
在这个视频中，我们已经看了各种各样的东西，对吧。
So, we looked at how to get specific information: which day of the year, which month, which year, and all that kind
所以，我们看了如何获得具体的信息：一年中的哪一天，哪一个月，哪一年，以及所有这些
of stuff.
的东西。
We also looked at getting generic information; leap year, is it a leap year,
我们还研究了如何获得通用信息；闰年，是否是闰年。
what is,
什么是。
what is the number of days in the current year.
本年度的天数是多少。
what is the number of days in current month.
当前月份的天数是多少。
And, we also looked at different operations to add  number of days, months, years, and subtract years, and
而且，我们还研究了不同的操作，以增加日数、月数、年数，以及减去年数，等等。
stuff like that.
诸如此类的操作。
The interesting thing to note is that very similar APIs exist on the LocalDateTime class as well.
值得注意的是，在LocalDateTime类中也存在非常类似的API。
So, on LocalDateTime class,
所以，在LocalDateTime类上。
if I create a instance of it right now, DateTime.now( ), there are very similar methods present.
如果我现在创建一个实例，DateTime.now( )，就有非常类似的方法存在。
However, in addition to the usual ones,
然而，除了通常的方法之外。
so let's say I want to do a plus, the LocalDateTime not only allows plusDays, plusMonths, plusYears,
所以，假设我想做一个加法，LocalDateTime不仅允许加日、加月、加年。
and plusWeeks, but it also allows plusSeconds, plusHours, and plusMinutes.
和plusWeeks，而且还允许plusSeconds、plusHours和plusMinutes。
So, all that I had to do was now.plus( ) and press tab and it would show all the options present. So,
因此，我所要做的就是now.plus( )，然后按tab键，它就会显示所有的选项。所以。
LocalDateTime provides all the options that are present for the LocalDate plus it allows you options
LocalDateTime提供了LocalDate的所有选项，而且它允许你选择
to play with hours, minutes, and seconds, and nanoseconds as well. So, over here what you are seeing in here
小时、分钟和秒，以及纳秒。所以，在这里你看到的是
is nanoseconds.
是纳秒。
So, that's basically what the LocalDateTime provides. So, similar to adding, you would also be able to get
所以，这基本上就是LocalDateTime提供的东西。所以，与添加类似，你也能得到
different information, right. So, now.get( ), you would be able to get minute, you'd be able to
不同的信息，对吧。所以，now.get( )，你就可以得到分钟，你就可以得到
get second,
得到秒。
you'll be able to get nano,
你将能够得到纳米。
and you'd be able to get the hour as well.
而且你也能得到小时数。
I'd recommend you to try and play around with the LocalDateTime API on your own and try and find out more
我建议你自己试着玩一玩LocalDateTime API，并尝试找出更多的
things about it. In this video,
关于它的事情。在这个视频中。
we looked at few of the important methods that are present on the LocalDate class.
我们看了LocalDate类中的一些重要方法。
We looked at how to play with it.
我们研究了如何使用它。
We also looked at a few methods which are present in the LocalDateTime.
我们还看了LocalDateTime中的一些方法。
In the next video, we will explore a few more things about the LocalDate and the LocalDateTime classes.
在下一个视频中，我们将探讨更多关于LocalDate和LocalDateTime类的东西。
Until then, bye bye.
在那之前，再见了。